Finding Aid for the George Schaefer Papers LSC.0588
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 3: Hallmark Hall of Fame, 1953-1982; 48 boxes
  - Subseries 3C: Production files., 1953-1982.
    - The Fantasticks--Production and format., 15 items. (Box 23, Folder 1)
      Stills and assorted printed materials.
    - The Fantasticks--Publicity., ca. 30 items. (Box 23, Folder 2)
      Press releases, press kit, slide, and assorted printed materials.
    - The Fantasticks--Sheet music--Bass., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - The Fantasticks--Sheet music--Cello., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - The Fantasticks--Sheet music--Chorus., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - The Fantasticks--Sheet music--Chorus, percussion, drums, violin., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - The Fantasticks--Sheet music--Drums., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - The Fantasticks--Sheet music--Guitar., 1 item. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - The Fantasticks--Sheet music--Harp., 1 item. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - The Fantasticks--Sheet music--Horn 1., 1 item. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - The Fantasticks--Sheet music--Horn 2., 1 item. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - The Fantasticks--Sheet music--Piano., 1 item. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - The Fantasticks--Sheet music--Reed 1., 1 item. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - The Fantasticks--Sheet music--Reed 2., 1 item. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - The Fantasticks--Sheet music--Reed 3., 1 item. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - The Fantasticks--Sheet music--Reed 4., 1 item. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - The Fantasticks--Sheet music--"This plum is too ripe.", 1 item. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - The Fantasticks--Sheet music--Trombone., 1 item. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - The Fantasticks--Sheet music--Trumpet., 1 item. (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - The Fantasticks--Sheet music--Viola., 1 item. (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - The Fantasticks--Sheet music--Violin A-B., 1 item. (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - The Fantasticks--Sheet music--Violin C., 1 item. (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - The Fantasticks--Vocal score., 1 item. (Box 25, Folder 9)
      By Harvey Schmidt and Tom Jones.
    - The File on Devlin--Clearance., 4 items. (Box 26, Folder 1)
      Correspondence with Sol Cornberg, and a signed agreement with designer Noel Taylor; lists.
    - The File on Devlin--Key sheets., 79 items. (Box 26, Folder 2)
      Key sheets, stills, and black and white photographs.
    - The File on Devlin--Legal file., 26 items. (Box 26, Folder 3)
      Signed contracts and agreements,and correspondence regarding P& W Remittance Report; AFTRA Production Report.
    - The File on Devlin--Production and format., 7 items. (Box 26, Folder 4)
      Cast list, production list, operational schedule, scene and prop breakdown, correspondence, synopsis.
    - The File on Devlin--Publicity., 10 items. (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - The File on Devlin--Script., 1 item. (Box 26, Folder 6)
      Annotated, as aired.
    - Gideon--Artcards., 31 items. (Box 27)
      Opening and closing artcards for Gideon.
    - Gideon--Audio and film (folder 1 of 3)., 5 items. (Box 28)
      1 sync track 8, 15 ips; 1 composite, 15 ips; 3 LPs of pre- recordings.
    - Gideon--Audio and film (folder 2 of 3)., 6 items. (Box 29)
      3 pre-recordings: 1 master mono full track (15 ips), two copies (1 7.5 ips, 1 15 ips); 2 Hallmark mono reels; "September Song" by Walter Huston; sound tape.
    - Gideon--Audio and film (folder 3 of 3)., 3 items. (Box 30)
      1 teaser 35mm: magnetic dubbed master, final dub, 3-stripe reel; 1 Rams horn: 1/4" master, includes studio work sheet; 1 untitled sound tape.
    - Gideon--Correspondence., ca. 50 items. (Box 31, Folder 1)
      Fan mail and letters from Foote, Cone & Belding, Hallmark, NBC, Hallmark, Casting, and GSS.
    - Gideon--Legal., ca. 50 items. (Box 31, Folder 2)
      Correspondence and signed agreements and contracts.
    - Gideon--Photographs., 70 items. (Box 31, Folder 3)
      Negatives, stills, and key sheets.
    - Gideon--Production and format., 10 items. (Box 31, Folder 4)
      Correspondence, sheet music, and assorted printed materials.
    - Gideon--Publicity., ca. 50 items. (Box 31, Folder 5)
      Playbill, portfolio, press releases, clippings and assorted printed materials.
    - Gideon--Script (folder 1 of 2)., 2 items. (Box 31, Folder 6)
      Drafts.
    - Gideon--Script (folder 2 of 2)., 2 items. (Box 32, Folder 1)
      Annotated and revised.
    - Give us Barabbas!--Script (3 of 5)., 5 items. (Box 32, Folder 10)
      Original annotated.
    - Gideon--Set design., 1 item. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Give us Barabbas!--Correspondence., 5 items. (Box 32, Folder 3)
      Fan mail and letters from Foote, Cone & Belding and Hallmark.
    - Give us Barabbas!--Production and format., 6 items. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Give us Barabbas!--Publicity., 10 items. (Box 32, Folder 5)
      Press releases and clippings.
    - Give us Barabbas!--Repeat (folder 1 of 2)., ca. 30 items. (Box 32, Folder 6)
      Contract, correspondence, press releases, slide, portfolio, clippings for the first rerun.
    - Give us Barabbas!--Repeat (folder 2 of 2)., ca. 50 items. (Box 32, Folder 7)
      Contract, correspondence, press releases, slide, portfolio, clippings for the second and third reruns.
    - Give us Barabbas!--Script (folder 1 of 5)., 1 item. (Box 32, Folder 8)
      First draft annotated.
    - Give us Barabbas!--Script (folder 2 of 5)., 1 item. (Box 32, Folder 9)
      Hartung revision.
    - Give us Barabbas!--Script (folder 4 of 5)., 5 items. (Box 33, Folder 1)
      Rewrite anotated.
    - Give us Barabbas!--Script (folder 5 of 5)., 3 items. (Box 33, Folder 2)
      Schaefer revision.
    - Golden Child--Clippings., ca. 20 items. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Golden Child--Correspondence., ca. 100 items. (Box 33, Folder 4)
      Fan mail and letters from Paul Engle, Foote, Cone, and Belding, and Hallmark.
    - Golden Child--Key sheets., 28 items. (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Golden Child--Production and format., 9 items. (Box 33, Folder 6)
      Assorted printed materials. See also box 78 for 4 LPs for acts 1-3. See also box 80 for music scores for acts 1-3.
    - Golden Child--Publicity., 15 items. (Box 33, Folder 7)
      Correspondence, news releases and assorted printed materials(see oversize folder 81 for poster).
    - Golden Child--Script., 3 items. (Box 33, Folder 8)
      Revised, with supporting production material.
    - The Green Pastures--Script., 1 item. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - The Holy Terror--Correspondence., ca. 50 items. (Box 34, Folder 2)
      Fan mail and letters from Foote, Cone & Belding, and NBC.
    - The Holy Terror--Production and format., 10 items. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - The Holy Terror--Publicity., ca. 20 items. (Box 34, Folder 4)
      Playbill, portfolio, slide, stills, press releases and clippings (see oversize folder 81 for poster).
    - The Holy Terror--Script., 3 items. (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Inherit the Wind--Clippings., ca. 25 items. (Box 34, Folder 6)
      Newspaper clippings and reviews.
    - Inherit the Wind--Correspondence., ca. 50 items. (Box 34, Folder 7)
      Fan mail and letters from NBC.
    - Inherit the Wind--Key sheets., ca. 30 items. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Inherit the Wind--Legal file (folder 1 of 2)., ca. 20 items. (Box 35, Folder 2)
      Signed agreements and contracts, correspondnece.
    - Inherit the Wind--Legal file (folder 2 of 2)., ca. 25 items. (Box 35, Folder 3)
      AFTRA agreements.
    - Inherit the Wind--Production and format., ca. 10 items. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Inherit the Wind--Publicity., ca. 10 items. (Box 35, Folder 5)
      Playbill, press releases, sketches, clippings, and assorted printed materials.
    - Inherit the Wind--Script., 1 item. (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - The Invincible Mr. Disraeli--Correspondence., ca. 50 items. (Box 35, Folder 7)
      Fan mail, and letters from Foote, Cone & Belding, Hallmark, and NBC.
    - The Invincible Mr. Disraeli--Production and format., ca. 15 items. (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - The Invincible Mr. Disraeli--Publicity., 9 items. (Box 36, Folder 1)
      Playbill, portfolio, press releases, clippings, slide, and assorted printed materials.
    - The Invincible Mr. Disraeli--Script., 1 item. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - The Joke and the Valley--Correspondence., ca. 50 items. (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - The Joke and the Valley--Production and format., 10 items. (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - The Joke and the Valley--Publicity., 15 items. (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - The Joke and the Valley--Script., 1 item. (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Lamp at Midnight--Correspondence., ca. 50 items. (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Lamp at Midnight--Production and format., 13 items. (Box 36, Folder 8)
      2 set drawings and assorted printed materials.
    - Lamp at Midnight--Publicity., ca. 25 items. (Box 37, Folder 1)
      Playbill, press releases, producer's report and clippings (see oversize folder 81 for poster).
    - Lamp at Midnight--Script., 1 item. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Little Moon of Alban--Clippings., ca. 20 items. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Little Moon of Alban--Contracts., ca. 25 items. (Box 37, Folder 4)
      Correspondence, signed agreements and contracts, P& W Remittance Report and AFTRA Production Report.
    - Little Moon of Alban--Correspondence., ca. 25 items. (Box 37, Folder 5)
      Fan mail and letters from Foote, Cone & Belding and NBC.
    - Little Moon of Alban--Key sheets., 32 items. (Box 37, Folder 6)
      Proof sheets and an 8 x 10 negative.
    - Little Moon of Alban--Milberg production., 15 items. (Box 37, Folder 7)
      Fan mail, still, clippings, script, and assorted printed materials.
    - Little Moon of Alban--Production and format., 7 items. (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Little Moon of Alban--Publicity., 32 items. (Box 38, Folder 1)
      Press releases, program notes, clippings, and assorted printed materials.
    - Little Moon of Alban--Script., 13 items. (Box 38, Folder 2)
      As aired, with supporting production materials.
    - Love Among the Ruins--Production file., ca. 50 items. (Box 38, Folder 3)
      Correspondence, casting information, and press releases (never made).
    - Macbeth--Allen and Overy., ca. 150 items. (Box 38, Folder 4)
      Correspondence, legal issues, and billing.
    - Macbeth--British Lion Films Unlimited., ca. 150 items. (Box 38, Folder 5)
      Correspondence and contracts regarding production and billing.
    - Macbeth--Budget., 15 items. (Box 38, Folder 6)
      Reports and cost sheets.
    - Macbeth--Correspondence., ca. 150 items. (Box 39, Folder 1)
      Fan mail and letters from MGM, Judith Anderson, Maurice Evans, and Phil C. Samuel.
    - Macbeth--Films Incorporated., ca. 150 items. (Box 39, Folder 2)
      Correspondence and invoices.
    - Macbeth--Foote, Cone, and Belding., ca. 150 items. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Macbeth--Gillon, Donald T., ca. 150 items. (Box 39, Folder 4)
      Correspondence and contracts prmarily regarding the cost of the production.
    - Macbeth--Hallmark., 4 items. (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Macbeth--Hutton, Clayton., 1 item. (Box 39, Folder 6)
      Hardcover book: Macbeth: the making of the film (London: Max Parrish).
    - Macbeth--International Film Distributors., ca. 30 items. (Box 39, Folder 7)
      Correspondence, billing, and contracts.
    - Macbeth--John Pearson International., ca. 30 items. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Macbeth--Miscellaneous., ca. 50 items. (Box 40, Folder 2)
      Script-reading guide, catalog, assorted correspondence, and expense material.
    - Macbeth--Photographs., ca. 120 items. (Box 40, Folder 3)
      Slides, black and white photographs and stills.
    - Macbeth--Production and format., ca. 100 items. (Box 40, Folder 4)
      Ratings, profit projections, actor biographies, set designs, and assorted printed materials. See also box 78 for 2 LPs marked "Macbeth exc. all bands identical" dated 11/10/60 and 11/17/60.
    - Macbeth--Prominent Films., ca. 50 items. (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Macbeth--Publicity., 15 items. (Box 40, Folder 6)
      Advertising, playbill, clippings, and assorted printed materials (see oversize folder 81 for poster).
    - Macbeth--Publicity--England., ca. 20 items. (Box 41, Folder 1)
      English release: playbill, press releases, and assorted printed materials (see oversize folder 81 for poster).
    - Macbeth--Publicity--United States (folder 1 of 2)., ca. 30 items. (Box 41, Folder 2)
      American releases: miscallaneous publicity and production materials, and press releases.
    - Macbeth--Publicity--United States (folder 2 of 2)., ca. 30 items. (Box 41, Folder 3)
      American release: clippings and assorted printed material.
    - Macbeth--Roadshow Distributors., ca. 30 items. (Box 41, Folder 4)
      Includes correspondence, billing,and contract material from Marshall Schacker.
    - Macbeth--Script., 1 item. (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Macbeth--Technicolor Limited., 5 items. (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Macbeth--Warner Brothers., ca. 15 items. (Box 41, Folder 7)
      Correspondence and billing material.
    - The Magnificent Yankee--Correspondence., ca. 50 items. (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - The Magnificent Yankee--Production and format., 2 items. (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - The Magnificent Yankee--Publicity., ca. 50 items. (Box 42, Folder 1)
      Playbills, press releases, press kit, slide, portfolio, still and clippings (see oversize folder 81 for poster). See also box for 79 for 1 sound reel of Oliver Wendell Holmes on his 90th b-day.
    - The Magnificent Yankee--Repeat., 9 items. (Box 42, Folder 2)
      Correspondence, press releases, and clippings for rerun (see oversize folder 81 for poster).
    - The Magnificent Yankee--Script., 2 items. (Box 42, Folder 3)
      Annotated, with music cues.
    - The Patriots--Correspondence., ca. 50 items. (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - The Patriots--Production and format., ca. 10 items. (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - The Patriots--Publicity., 11 items. (Box 42, Folder 6)
      Still, portfolio, press release, and clippings.
    - The Patriots--Script (folder 1 of 2)., 1 item. (Box 42, Folder 7)
      Annotated, with supporting production material.
    - The Patriots--Script (folder 2 of 2)., 1 item. (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - A Punt, a Pass, and a Prayer--Correspondence., ca. 50 items. (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Letters from Foote, Cone & Belding, Hallmark, NBC, and David Mark.
    - A Punt, a Pass, and a Prayer--Production and format., ca. 50 items. (Box 43, Folder 2)
      Two set design diagrams, shots of locations, and assorted printed materials.
    - A Punt, a Pass, and a Prayer--Publicity., ca. 50 items. (Box 43, Folder 3)
      Playbill, press releases, actor biographies, clippings, and assorted printed materials.
    - A Punt, a Pass, and a Prayer--Script., 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Pygmalion--Clippings., ca. 25 items. (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Pygmalion--Correspondence., ca. 50 items. (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Pygmalion--Production and format., 25 items. (Box 43, Folder 7)
      Cast lists, production materials, and key sheets.
    - Pygmalion--Publicity., ca. 25 items. (Box 43, Folder 8)
      Press releases, portfolio, slide, clippings, and assorted printed materials.
    - Pygmalion--Script., 1 item. (Box 44, Folder 1)
      Fully revised, with supporting production materials.
    - Saint Joan--Correspondence., 10 items. (Box 44, Folder 2)
      Fan mail and letters from Foote, Cone & Belding, Hallmark, NBC, and Video Tape Center.
    - Saint Joan--Production and format., ca. 150 items. (Box 44, Folder 3)
      Assorted printed materials. See also box 79 for 2 35mm effects films from Reeves Sound Studios: 1 marked "thunder & lightning from 10 Commandments" and 1 marked "thunder & lightning from Rainmaker."
    - Saint Joan--Publicity., ca. 25 items. (Box 44, Folder 4)
      Playbill, press releases and clippings (see oversize folder 81 for poster).
    - Shangri-La--Clippings., ca. 25 items. (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Shangri-La--Correspondence., ca. 20 items. (Box 44, Folder 6)
      Fan mail and letters from Hallmark.
    - Shangri-La--Lawrence and Lee., 15 items. (Box 44, Folder 7)
      Correspondence from Jermone Lawrence and Robert Lee, and sheet music for Second Time in Love.
    - Shangri-La--Production and format., ca. 25 items. (Box 44, Folder 8)
      Cast and production lists, rehearsal schedule, key sheets, and assorted printed materials.
    - Shangri-La--Publicity., ca. 25 items. (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Soldier in Love--Correspondence., ca. 150 items. (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Soldier in Love--Production and format., ca. 25 items. (Box 45, Folder 2)
      Production materals, and "The Story of Montacute and Its House" by H. Avray Tipping (London: Country Life Limited, for the National Trust).
    - Soldier in Love--Publicity., ca. 25 items. (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Soldier in Love--Script., 1 item. (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - The Teahouse of the August Moon--Clippings., ca. 20 items. (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - The Teahouse of the August Moon--Correspondence., ca. 25 items. (Box 45, Folder 6)
      Letters from Foote, Cone, and Belding.
    - The Teahouse of the August Moon--Legal file., ca. 20 items. (Box 45, Folder 7)
      Signed agreements and assorted legal documents.
    - The Teahouse of the August Moon--Production file., ca. 25 items. (Box 46, Folder 1)
      Billing materials, memoranda, cast and production list, scene sequence, and key sheets.
    - The Teahouse of the August Moon--Publicity., ca. 30 items. (Box 46, Folder 2)
      Playbill, press releases, portfolio, slides, clippings.
    - The Teahouse of the August Moon--Set design., 15 items. (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - The Teahouse of the August Moon--Script., 1 item. (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - The Tempest--Correspondence., ca. 25 items. (Box 46, Folder 5)
      Fan mail and letters from Foote, Cone & Belding.
    - The Tempest--Production and format., ca. 245 items. (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - The Tempest--Publicity., ca. 30 items. (Box 46, Folder 7)
      Press releases and assorted printed materials.
    - The Tempest--Repeat (folder 1 of 2)., ca. 25 items. (Box 47, Folder 1)
      Correspondence, production and format materials for rerun.
    - The Tempest--Repeat (folder 2 of 2)., ca. 25 items. (Box 47, Folder 2)
      Slides, portfolio, press releases, clippings for rerun.
    - Time Remembered--Correspondence., ca. 25 items. (Box 47, Folder 3)
      Fan mail and letters from Foote, Cone, and Belding.
    - Time Remembered--Musical., ca. 25 items. (Box 47, Folder 4)
      Correspondence, contract, outline and other assorted printed materials. See also box 77 for 1954 score for Leocadia.
    - Time Remembered--Production and format., 15 items. (Box 47, Folder 5)
      Assorted printed materials and sheet music for Time Remembered.
    - Time Remembered--Publicity., ca. 20 items. (Box 47, Folder 6)
      Press releases, playbill, portfolio, clippings, slide.
    - Time Remembered--Scripts., 2 items. (Box 47, Folder 7)
      Revised and taped.
    - Truman at Potsdam--Clippings., ca. 50 items. (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Truman at Potsdam--Script., 1 item. (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Victoria Regina--Correspondence., ca. 25 items. (Box 48, Folder 1)
      Fan mail and letters from Foote, Cone, and Belding and Hallmark.
    - Victoria Regina--Production and format., ca. 30 items. (Box 48, Folder 2)
      Cast list, taping schedules, sheet music for "Drink to me only with thine eyes," research materials including black and white photographs of Prince Albert, Queen Victoria, and Buckingham Palace, and assorted printed materials.
    - Victoria Regina--Publicity., ca. 30 items. (Box 48, Folder 3)
      Press releases, portfolio, clippings, slide.
    - Victoria Regina--Repeat., ca. 15 items. (Box 48, Folder 4)
      Correspondence, production and format materials, and publicity for rerun.
    - Victoria Regina--Set design., 18 items. (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Victoria Regina--Script., 1 item. (Box 48, Folder 6)
      Revised.
    - Winterset--Correspondence., ca. 25 items. (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Winterset--Production and format., 10 items. (Box 48, Folder 8)
      Billing materials, scene schedule, cast list, and a tribute to Maxwell Anderson by Mark Connelly.
    - Winterset--Publicity., ca. 30 items. (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 3D: Scrapbooks., 1959-1969.
    Scrapbooks of publicity and clippings related to Hallmark Hall of Fame productions. Arranged chronologically by television season.
    - 1959-1960 season., 1 item. (Box 49, Folder 1)
      Clippings and publicity material related to Winterset, A Doll's House, The Borrowed Christmas, The Tempest, Turn the Key Deftly, the Hallmark script fund, Cradle Song, and Captain Brassbound's Conversion.
    - 1960-1961 season., 1 item. (Box 50, Folder 1)
      Clippings and publicity material related to Shangri-La, Macbeth, Golden Child, Time Remembered, Give us Barabbas!, The Joke and the Valley.
    - 1961-1962 season., 1 item. (Box 51, Folder 1)
      Clippings and publicity material related to Macbeth, Victoria Regina, Arsenic and Old Lace, and Give us Barabbas!(repeat).
    - 1962-1963 season., 1 item. (Box 52, Folder 1)
      Clippings and publicity material related to Teahouse of the August Moon, Cyrano de Bergerac, Pygmalion, and The Invincible Mr. Disraeli.
    - Hallmark Blue Book--1963-1964 season., 1 item. (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Clippings and publicity material related to assorted Hallmark Hall of Fame TV dramas.
    - 1963-1964 season., 1 item. (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - 1964-1965 season., 1 item. (Box 55, Folder 1)
      Clippings and publicity material related to The Fantasticks, The Magnificent Yankee, and The Holy Terror.
    - 1965-1966 season., 1 item. (Box 56, Folder 1)
      Clippings and publicity material.
    - 1966-1967 season., 1 item. (Box 57, Folder 1)
      Clippings and publicity material related to the Hallmark Hall of Fame 1966- 1967 season.
    - 1967-1968 season., 1 item. (Box 58, Folder 1)
      Clippings and publicity material related to Compass Productions' 1967-1968 season, including St. John, Elizabeth the Queen, Give Us Barabbas, The Admirable Crichton, A Punt, a Pass, and a Prayer, Hallmark Hall of Fame publicity, and the Emmy awards.
- Series 4: Miscellaneous, 1957-1991; 3 boxes
  Arranged in three subseries:
  4A. Compass Productions, 1957-1973 (1 box).
  4B. Production materials, 1961-1976 (1 box).
  UCLA, 1970-1991 (1 box).
  - Subseries 4A: Compass Productions, 1957-1973
    Assorted files related to George Schaefer's production company. Arranged alphabetically by subject of the file contents.
    - Below-the-line estimates., ca. 50 items. (Box 59, Folder 1)
      Estimated and actual costs, invoices, payment schedules, cost reports, and correspondence, related to Compass productions.
    - Charges., ca. 30 items. (Box 59, Folder 2)
      Charge sheets and invoices for various productions.
    - Elliot, Mike., ca. 15 items. (Box 59, Folder 3)
      CTV Division (production and distribution of video cassettes). Correspondence, clippings, 'cassette project' chart, and a list of authors, titles, and publishers.
    - Financial Reports (folder 1 of 2)., 6 items. (Box 59, Folder 4)
      Reports by fiscal year, pulled from a binder.
    - Financial Reports (folder 2 of 2)., 8 items. (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Property list and availabilities (folder 1 of 2)., 1 item. (Box 59, Folder 6)
      A-D.
    - Property list and availabilities (folder 2 of 2)., 1 item. (Box 59, Folder 7)
      E-Z.
    - Television ratings., 7 items. (Box 60, Folder 1)
      Includes Trendex, Arbitron, Nielsen ratings for productions, correspondence, and a clipping.
  - Subseries 4B: Production materials, 1961-1976
    Correspondence, showbills, and miscellanous materials related to assorted productions. Arranged alphabetically by subject of the file contents.
    - Almirall, Lloyd., 15 items. (Box 60, Folder 2)
      Correspondence with Almirall, an attorney for Breed, Abbott and Morgan.